[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
-Master. -Master.
Master.
The Young Master...
Master, be careful.
What happened?
Where is Yuanfan?
Master,
when I got here, the Young Master was already gone.
All I found was the blood left on the bed.
Get everyone in the Salt Gang to look for my son!
Yes, Master.
Wait!
Master.
Go find those sorcerers!
If they dare to deceive me,
I will skin them alive!
[A Prophet]
[Episode 21]
Master.
They are back.
They said they prepared a gift for you.
Come on in.
Sect Master.
What an eyesore.
Send him to the woodshed.
The weather is changing.
I guess it's going to rain.
In a few hours,
the Salt Gang will come out in full force.
There are hundreds of them,
and every one of them can fight.
Our Tianxiang Sect
is probably doomed this time.
Why didn't you just kill Shangguan Chengming?
If you killed him,
we could just end this.
Cut the crap.
It's all because someone tried to use me as a pawn.
Really?
Who?
How did it go?
I turned a killing trap
into a money-making trap.
I wonder if you like it.
I like making money.
Tell me about it.
Given Zhang Yinhua's tuberculosis,
he won't last more than a month.
Even if we trap Li Ling's soul,
when Zhang Yinhua ends up dead
and word gets out,
how can others still trust us?
The double-sided trap can last for 50 years,
all thanks to your foresight—
we do soul-trapping rituals
for whoever can make a fortune.
Now,
Zhang Yinhua is about to fall.
You're only worried about
how to keep this up after his death.
Exactly.
And then?
Zhang Yuanfan will be the future head of the Zhang family.
As long as he trusts us completely,
this trap will not end
for the next 50 years.
Then what do you plan to do?
I hope you can do me a small favor.
Arrange a killing trap?
No killing.
Master.
You're here.
I was just pondering over it.
I watched you grow up.
Among the Batous in our sect,
you're the quickest-witted.
You can both figure out the bigger picture
and get small things done efficiently.
You've made me plenty of money
and also caused me as much trouble.
Master.
I was wrong.
What did you do wrong?
I shouldn't have saved Li Ling.
So you mean this.
It seems that you've saved more than just her.
Sect Master.
Liu Xijiao and the others
were all carefully trained by the sect for years.
It would be such a pity for them to die in the trap.
How about we let them flee first?
And when our sect
needs them,
we can get them back to serve.
Also, please rest assured,
they have all sworn on their lives
never to reveal a word about it.
Look at you.
Impressive.
You're far-sighted and considerate.
Sect Master,
I am willing to accept my punishment.
Let me show you something interesting.
You gave this to Liu Xijiao, didn't you?
Seems like she doesn't need it anymore.
[Verdict from the Underworld]
Are you a human or a ghost?
Where am I?
City God Temple,
the first pass to the underworld.
Stop fooling me!
I was sleeping at home.
Then I woke up and ended up here.
How did I die?
Tell me!
Everyone...
Says so.
Master,
I ran into a female ghost by chance yesterday.
She was trapped in the mortal world
and begged me to take her back.
Not until I took her back to this family
did I realize
that her soul was trapped.
I want to help the Zhang family handle this,
but my power is not strong enough.
Master, please help me.
This matter of the Zhang family
is not that simple.
I need to think it through.
Yuanfan...
I suffered so much...
Yuanfan.
Yuanfan...
You betrayed me.
Open the door! Help!
Yuanfan.
You put me through this.
Open the door!
Help!
Yuanfan...
Don't come over!
Open the door! Help!
Master, open the door!
Help! Help!
Master!
Master, save me.
I am Zhang Yuanfan, the Young Master of the Zhang family
you mentioned.
Why are you here?
I was sleeping at home.
I woke up and ended up here!
Yuanfan...
You can see Li Ling?
Isn't she right out there?
Did you drink the talisman water
I gave your Zhang family?
I did drink it. I drank it all.
Why did you still end up dead after drinking it?
I don't know.
Did you pee after drinking
the talisman water?
You can't pee that talisman water out!
Peeing it out would lose its effect!
Master,
how could I hold my pee?
You're already in the City God Temple now.
This is the first pass to the underworld.
Once the door opens,
take your verdict,
remove your living registration,
have it stamped with the City God's seal,
and you can go to the underworld.
I'm really dead?
Yuanfan...
Master, Master,
I beg you to take me back to the mortal world.
As long as you take me back,
my father will pay you
as much as you want!
My father never hesitates to spend money for me.
I am also a filial son.
I still need to take care of him.
Master, I'm begging you.
Even if I take you back,
in a few days...
Yuanfan...
You will still come down here.
Could it be that if I ascend to the mortal world,
Li Ling can still chase me there to kill me?
You killed Li Ling and trapped her soul
soon after she married into your family.
There's no way she won't cause you trouble.
I had no other choice.
Given my father's poor health,
he couldn't hold on for much longer.
I just talked
to my master about this matter.
If he is willing to lend a hand,
it'll take him
less than 7 days to annihilate this evil ghost, Li Ling.
However,
Li Ling may not be the one
trying to harm you, I'm afraid.
Then who else could it be?
This person is very close to you.
Xiaomei?
Dingxiang?
Fengxia?
Zhen?
It's your father,
Zhang Yinhua.
He wanted to trap Li Ling's soul to prolong his lifespan
but failed.
Even if he takes in another concubine now
and treats her well,
his health
probably won't hold out until then.
Therefore,
he wants to trap someone who is closest to him
and will never betray him.
I am his son.
Our Zhang family has had only one heir for 3 generations respectively.
Would he end his own bloodline?
Disciple,
we are both cultivators.
Do not interfere with other people's karma.
Just send him back to the mortal world.
Whether it's a blessing or retribution
depends on his fate.
Thank you, Master!
Go!
Li Ling isn't the only one
trapped in your Zhang family's place.
Do you know these people?
Stepmother?
Second Stepmother?
And Concubine Liu?
They can neither return to the mortal world
nor go to the underworld now.
They can only wander around here.
Will they hurt me then?
Xijiao?
Yes, of course.
They died for your Zhang family.
If you break into the trap,
we will kill you!
Go!
Why harm me?
My father trapped their souls, not me!
That's why they say,
"A son pays his father's debts."
Isn't trapping souls meant to protect our family?
It protects your father.
Otherwise, he would have died 20 years ago.
He's got all the boons,
while the banes
are coming to you, of course.
No way, Master.
I beg you.
Please save me, Master.
I'm begging you!
Annihilate their souls,
and you can return to the mortal world.
Yuanfan.
I am Concubine Liu,
Xijiao,
Liu Xijiao!
Concubine Liu...
I remember you.
Yuanfan...
Don't come closer.
Don't come any closer.
Stay back.
Yuanfan...
Wait.
Disciple,
let him go.
If my father could use you to prolong his lifespan,
why can't I?
I want to live.
I want to survive!
A son pays his father's debts.
He's got all the boons,
while the banes...
Yuanfan...
Are coming to you, of course.
Go to hell.
All of you, go to hell!
No!
These three people
are my gift in return to you.
Jiang Feiyan let these female Abaos go.
You know the sect rules.
I've been merciful enough.
I had Chief Batou drug them.
Although they've become deranged,
they can still live for a while.
If they weren't of use to your trap,
they'd already be dead.
They are not pawns!
They are human!
Do you care so little about human lives?
Shout a bit louder, and he will wake up,
and she would have died for nothing.
Trampling on human lives—
is this what the Tianxiang Sect calls "upholding justice"?
"Upholding justice."
Let me tell you what justice is.
Whoever holds the power
is justice.
Whether I talk sense or nonsense,
as long as people like him all believe it,
that is justice.
I know you can't kill anyone.
You can't do it.
But you must pass this test,
so I had to give you a push.
Didn't we agree not to kill?
Making money
is a bloody business.
When did Liu Xijiao
come back?
This person has nothing to do with you anymore.
Don't ask about her again.
According to the sect rules,
anyone who wants to leave must take 3 cuts and 6 stabs.
Today, in front of the Sect Master,
how could they still...
Our Sect Master is soft-hearted.
He gave the girls a chance
to come back and help set a trap.
That's right.
Yes.
After this trap is done,
they will be allowed to leave.
Listen,
this girl will no longer
be a member of our sect.
You and she were just not meant to be together in this life,
got it?
Let's go.
Glad that she left.
Good to know she left.
Knock as you please.
This one is
made of genuine nanmu wood,
with a 9-inches-thick base
and flawless planks.
It can withstand any amount of knocking.
I knew
you would definitely show mercy
and come buy a coffin for that girl.
See?
I specifically kept the best one
just for you.
It won't cost much.
Just 3 gold bars.
I'll take this coffin.
I'll pay you
when the trap is done.
You really thought
those female Abaos could escape?
You know what?
The Sect Master has been watching you all along.
The Sect Master has already
seen through your thoughts.
I just don't get it.
If you want to do good deeds,
you can go be a teacher and join a revolution.
Or at least,
you can go become a monk in the mountains.
Why did you join our Tianxiang Sect?
I just feel sorry for that girl.
What's wrong with that?
Feel sorry for her?
In these times,
the world is awash with pitiful people.
For us swindlers,
if we can
end up lying in a coffin like this,
that will be the greatest blessing.
How bold you are.
How dare you come again?
Where is my son?
I've brought
your son back to you.
Yuanfan.
Yuanfan!
Don't worry, he's fine.
Be careful.
Young Master.
Yuanfan.
My boy.
My boy?
Li Ling...
Li Ling wants to kill me...
Don't let her come near.
Don't let her come any closer!
Keep her away from me.
Your son just came back from the underworld.
His soul fragments haven't fully returned yet.
Yuanfan.
Don't be afraid.
I am here with you.
Tell me
what happened.
Master!
Master, I beg you.
You must save me, Master!
I don't want to go back there again!
Master...
You may take your son back to his room to rest first.
Master, I'm scared...
Master...
Young Master.
Please get up, Young Master.
You're back home.
Save me.
Save me, Master.
Master!
Sir,
you have done a great favor for our Zhang family.
This is a gift to show our appreciation.
Sir,
I must say something in the first place.
This matter
is not over yet.
Li Ling's soul
is only temporarily suppressed by me.
It will take one week to completely annihilate it.
Be careful. Li Ling will come again this week.
She will come again?
She will not only come again
but also take advantage of your son's weak condition
to occupy his body.
Therefore, you must not mention the matter of Li Ling
and the soul trapping again.
If you bring it up,
you'll be summoning Li Ling's soul.
Before possessing your son's body,
Li Ling will bind him with evil energy,
leaving scratch marks on his body.
When that happens, you must keep your son's soul
and not give Li Ling any opportunity.
Tie him up!
What are you doing?
What? What are you doing?
Let me go!
You'll kill yourself scratching like that!
I'm itchy, so I scratch! What's wrong with that?
Father, tell them to let me go!
I'm itchier when you tie me,
Father!
Hurry up!
I won't scratch anymore.
Just tell them to let me go,
Father!
Let me go!
Master.
How is he doing now?
As you ordered,
we fed him the talisman water,
and he's been sleeping.
The Young Master's got ghost scratch marks all over his body,
even on his back
where he can't reach himself!
It must be
Li Ling coming for him.
Have a seat, Master.
I've been taking a turn
for the worse day by day.
Where is the girl I asked you to find?
I'm still working on it.
Why is it so hard to find one?
With my wealth, I can't even find a wife?
Go
buy one from those poor people who are selling
their daughters.
Understood.
Who is it?
Who?
Don't come over!
Don't come any closer!
Stay back!
Back!
I have money!
I can give you everything!
What are you all doing?
Make way!
Don't come any closer!
-Master. -Master.
Don't come over!
Stay back!
I have money!
I can give you everything I have!
Please spare me!
Open the door.
Don't come over!
Yuanfan.
Yuanfan!
Li Ling...
Li Ling has come for me.
[Zhang Residence]
What?
Does it disgust you?
You asked me to use eel blood,
and now I stink of it.
Eel blood is the most pungent.
Only by attracting bats to hit the door this way
could we make it sound like a ghost knocking.
Guess who I saw the other day?
Who?
Liu Xijiao!
Sect Master
didn't stoop to their level.
He had them help set a trap
and then let them go.
Sect Master is such a nice person,
like a living Buddha.
Young Master...
I have already
chosen the person.
In a few days,
you
can perform the soul-trapping ritual.
I've been watching
this child for a long time.
The child and the father live together
in poverty.
As long as I pay the family a little money,
the child will definitely follow me...
I think we should just forget it.
It's a very filial child,
young
and promising.
Are you really going to trap this child's soul?
The child's mother died early.
What's wrong with the child doing something for the father?
It's a perfect choice for soul trapping.
Close the door.
Li Ling may not be the one trying to harm you, I'm afraid.
Then who else could it be?
It's your father, Zhang Yinhua.
He can only trap someone who is closest to him
and will never betray him.
It protects your father.
Otherwise, he would have died 20 years ago.
He's got all the boons,
while the banes
are coming to you, of course.
Where's the handprint on the door?
What handprint?
Li Ling came last night.
The handprint she left
is gone!
It's gone!
Yuanfan.
Look at me.
Do you love me?
My boy, tell me,
do you love me?
Then tell me,
what's that water vat outside
for?
Isn't that used
to make your favorite pickles?
No!
No...
You use it to trap souls.
Trap souls.
Son,
I don't know what you're talking about.
Trap what?
I don't get what you mean.
Do you still remember this?
When you trapped Li Ling's soul,
her body...
her body was covered
with these marks scratched by ghosts.
What did you say?
Who?
My wife...
My wife, Li Ling!
Didn't you trap her soul
to prolong your lifespan?
I don't know the person you're talking about.
You're not going to live much longer.
You need to find someone.
You can't find anyone else,
so you want to seal my soul now.
You want to trap my soul, right?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Yuanfan,
I love you!
Do you love me?
You've never asked if I love you.
Why the sudden question?
Why are you asking me all of a sudden now?
I just want you to say it!
Do you love me?
I love you...
I love you to death!
You must keep your son's soul
before Li Ling possesses his body.
When you are alone with your son,
ask him
if he loves you.
You must stare him straight in the eyes
and make sure he answers this question.
[Yunhe Temple]
Master.
Sir,
why are you doing this?
I want to...
I want to trap my father's soul!
Did I hear you wrong,
or are you out of your mind?
You want to trap your father's soul?
That old man is already in the late stages of tuberculosis.
Yet he wants to use me to prolong his lifespan.
I know he's turned to you.
You must have received a lot of rewards from him.
But it doesn't matter!
Whatever he pays you,
I'll double it.
Good?
He is your father.
Are you sure about this?
There's no father in the world who doesn't care about his son.
Is he even human?
He always says my mother died early,
and it wasn't easy for him to raise me alone.
That's because he trapped my mother's soul.
Therefore,
trapping him
is me upholding justice!
I'll give you 3 more opium shops.
Let's do it together.
Let's uphold justice together.
"Disasters and blessings
are brought by humans."
You must think through
the consequences of this.
I have thought it through.
I'll kill him
and get my hands covered in blood.
And I'm leaving
the rest to you, Master.
Master!
Young Master...
The cellar!
Stop that brat now!
Be careful, Master.
Master.
Yuanfan.
My boy?
Yuanfan!
Young Master.
Murder!
Yuanfan,
my boy.
I am Zhang Yinhua.
Zhang Yinhua!
What are you doing?
Don't come over!
I am your father!
And you still want to kill me
and trap my soul?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Stop playing dumb with me!
What is this?
And what are these things?
Tell me, what are these?
Father,
tell me.
Do you love me?
Yes, I love you...
The entire Zhang family
will be mine.
Since you love me,
Father,
just stay here
and bless me with wealth and glory!
♪ The lantern waits for one ♪
♪ Who won't return ♪
♪ My eyes hide a sorrow beyond words ♪
♪ I ask for too much ♪
♪ Then blame fate ♪
♪ One step, one trap, one fall ♪
♪ Greed turns into a chain to trap the old love ♪
♪ Play with fire, yet people's foolishness will never burn away ♪
♪ Who pretends to be a saint in front of others ♪
♪ Yet turns around and wallows in the mundane world? ♪
♪ My greed burns away who I am ♪
♪ My anger clouds what I hold dear ♪
♪ My obsession keeps me from turning back ♪
♪ I keep my heart closed ♪
Let me go!
You're making me clean up your mess again, huh?
This case
is enough for you to claim credit with Director Wang.
You may be nosy,
but you're always doing
righteous things.
Why does a person like you
have to
stay with a bunch of swindlers?
You've also diligently worked on various cases
in Yucheng, Detective Guo.
Why does a person like you
have to
work for Director Wang?
Drink tea as you please,
but don't talk nonsense.
[Tomb of Liu Xijiao]
What's this?
Didn't Xijiao leave?
Liang,
There's something I never knew
how to tell you.
At this point...
I think I should tell you the truth.
Because I don't want to be
a swindler in front of you.
Liu Xijiao wasn't let go by the Sect Master.
The Sect Master got her killed.
I buried her with my own hands.
No way.
The Sect Master wouldn't kill the innocent.
The Sect Master wouldn't kill Liu Xijiao!
Liang.
I said, it's impossible!
The Sect Master treats us gofers so well!
Stop lying to yourself.
We experienced the Soul-Trapping Game together.
If we hadn't saved Li Ling,
she would be dead as well.
The Sect Master has drowned so many innocent girls
in water vats
just to continue
his scam that has lasted 50 years.
Eight years ago,
the Sect Master set a trap in Jianghuai,
ruining a family of the Wangs.
At that time,
only one person in the whole family survived.
He saw the bodies of his younger brother and younger sister
floating on the Nanxi River.
♪ Under the old city wall, that year the rain fell gently ♪
That only survivor
was me.
At that time, I only wanted to die,
♪ You walked by with an umbrella, saying loneliness didn't scare you ♪
but I met Jin Buhuan.
He told me the truth behind the whole thing.
♪ Later, a blade lay hidden within a smile ♪
Since then,
I've only had one thought in my mind.
As long as I can get revenge...
♪ An impulsive, spiteful remark cut deep into my heart ♪
I'm willing to learn anything.
♪ You know full well how weak I am ♪
Liang,
about what kind of person the Sect Master is
♪ Yet you always turn around ♪
and what kind of organization the Tianxiang Sect is,
♪ Shielding me from harsh words and cold daggers ♪
you have to see clearly on your own
and think it through.
♪ May you journey toward your future ♪
♪ Leave this stormy sea behind ♪
♪ Let the toxic love we shared ♪
♪ Be the moss that helps you grow ♪
♪ May you find your way out of the haze that is us ♪
♪ Leave me out of your story ♪
♪ Should freedom be your ultimate desire ♪
♪ I shall bloom for you in silence ♪
I'm sorry...
Xijiao...
I was too stupid.
I didn't protect you well.
I lost you.
Xijiao,
trust me.
♪ By the window, flowers withers as time passes ♪
I will definitely avenge your death.
Sect Master...
♪ You lean on the door with a smile and ask how long it takes to let go ♪
Just you wait.
[Jiulongpo Station, Yucheng]
♪ The blade draws near yet misses every time ♪
Not all girls
can get away clean
♪ The moment you do it, all that's left is a trembling embrace ♪
like Li Ling.
She sold her house
and can stay in Pangzhou for now.
In the future,
♪ May you journey toward your future ♪
she can also go to Nanyang
for peace.
Just one boat ticket to Nanyang
♪ Leave this stormy sea behind ♪
♪ Let the toxic love we shared ♪
costs enough to buy a girl from our sect.
I've explained everything
♪ Be the moss that helps you grow ♪
about Liu Xijiao to Liang.
♪ May you find your way out of the haze that is us ♪
He'll eventually know the truth,
♪ Leave me out of your story ♪
and he deserves to know
what kind of person
♪ Should freedom be your ultimate desire ♪
on earth the Sect Master is.
Did the Sect Master cause you any trouble
♪ I'll hold back and let you go ♪
for saving those girls?
Not yet.
I guess he has more ruthless tricks
waiting for me.
If possible,
I'd rather
die by your hands.
With me here,
you'll be fine.
[In the next episode]
The Fifth Batou and Shangguan Chengming
saved Paozi from the trap.
They were also the ones
who broke the trap.
Breaking the trap means breaking the rules.
Now you're talking to me about rules?
So what?
Either
you kill Jiang Feiyan,
or
I'll kill both of you
today.
The Tianxiang Sect has another rule.
We run scams for money but don't kill.
According to the rules you mentioned,
shouldn't everyone be killed today?